what up guy
I did I did on for the hata giraffes I
guess I'll do it for the term giraffe -
yeah Toyota giraffes are super sweet so
we got check it out this is a Skype and
in it yeah this one's a little used I
just pulled it out of my Toyota yeah so
they should go into production this week
we just ordered 200 boards a nice solid
feel to them
Toyota Moana we have a little bit more
room the Honda one you have to move way
to the right to get away from the
existing system Toyota one you just plug
it in like that it goes in I'm gonna
missus to the side then you can connect
well all the Wi-Fi with shiver or you
can connect this USB port to your Neo
pretty good pretty good
umm rav4 support Prius support
Alti SSP support coming to open pilot
someday
so so let's go Lisa I was driving around
that yesterday a few things we gotta fix
but yeah toyota support is real and yeah
i mean the way that we're supporting
things for the future is with giraffes
you check it out you got an Ethernet
port right down there you can plug that
into a neo it is a downside to Toyota
there's no continuous power available on
this connector so you have a few options
did Vivian talk to you about not here
it's Saturday
Leo is me
yeah but also the downside of Toyota is
there's no continuous power available on
this connector so we included a barrel
connector
and you can get 12 volts into there
however you'd like
so the cables we have actually run all
the way down to the ODB part o d OB d OB
deport I always say it wrong
um please show more what else you want
to say yeah so you guys a secret
internal debug board there's a secret
internal debug board we used to test me
us
um you plug a panda into it you plug in
do into it and connect them up together
this is what you first simulator if you
saw this simulator on Twitter what else
do I got to show wires and wires like
this one wires are terrible I hate wires
wires that was bright that's why we've
built solid drafts comma logo right
there the switches what are the switches
do so the switches let you turn on and
off the existing a tas system in your
car so if you want to proxy it if you
want to forward it you can do all that
with a giraffe so edgy that's a little
bit different so this switch 3 on the
honda one is for cam 2 switch 3 on the
Toyota giraffe is for enabling power
when there's ignition so yeah otherwise
you got to use this spiral connector
down at the bottom connect this to OBD
connect this to 4 lights
Oh B D yeah that's right
obd it's like n be deep but obd yeah one
more a little wedding today I could go
shower
yeah I gotta go shower I woke up and I
shipped the draft and I tried to fix
models models are kind of broken we have
new models coming up new models are
really cool machine learning is really
cool like oh yeah so that's it that's
the Toyota giraffe link to buy it is on
the wiki on Twitter and on slack thanks
for watching
she goes later